

# PRAPAS KHONG-ATTAGARN



- angna District, Bangkok, 10260
- prapas.k13@hotmail.com
- (+66)8-606-97918
- n prapas-k

# **INTRODUCE**

An ambitious and well-rounded graphic designer for 7 years with extensive experience in print design poster namecard and banner. Expect to working in tech area with very talented team, I have a passionate to Artificial intelligence to create innovative or combination of tech and design together for better results

# **EDUCATION**

Bachelor's Degree in Fine Arts, Major Communication Design Bangkok University 2012, GPA 2.62/4

# **LANGUAGES**



THAI - NATIVE





# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

• Graphic Designer @ OSCAR GRAPHIC for 3 months. (DEC 2019 - FEB 2020)

## Responsibilities

- Design, edit and develop an artwork offline media like banner, poster, sticker label and namecard.
- Produce some work pieces as well.

# <u>Achievements</u>

 Plan a time management and start the design to complete task in 1 or 2 hrs or more depending on the type of work. In 1 day handle 3-5 clients.
 Many clients trust and let me to be partner on new projects again.

## · Coordinator Designer @ DKSH (Thailand)

for 5 months. (NOV 2018 - APR 2019)

# Responsibilities

- Design space management events area to set position of furniture.
- Control the installation before the event day.
- Supports senior designer.

## **Achievements**

 Design space management ranging from 25 sqm. up to shop in the mall to support at least 50 customers.

# · Graphic Designer @ SIAM PARAGON DEVELOPMENT

for 5 years. (JUN 2012 - APR 2018)

# Responsibilities

- Design, edit and develop an artwork offline media like banner, poster and photo backdrop.
- Production control check pantone colour before produce.

## <u>Achievements</u>

- Design print media to promote events throughout the mall for both Thais and foreigners customers more than 10000 people.
- Reduce the cost of hiring an agency.
- Design support for another departments on avaerage 5 tasks per day.

## **COURSES**

Software Dev : Full-Stack Developer @ Generation TH. : on going
Web develop : HTML CSS PHP SQL @ Tutortong. : 3 months
3d Model : Zbrush @ Z-LA digital arts. : 3 months
Interior : 3ds Max @ Utahtd 3d tutor. : 3 months

## **CHARACTERISTICS**

INTJ AMBIVERT INTP

Introverted
 Independent

ThinkingLogicalProspectingGreativeJudgingFlexible

#### **STRENGTHS**

- · Open-Minded
- · Honest and Straightforward
- · Enjoys theoretical & abstract concepts
- · Good at listening
- · Takes criticism well
- Concentrate
- · Proactiveness

#### **CODING LANGUAGES**

PYTHON
PHP SQL

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Self learning javascript from Carousel bootstrap framework by rewrite Jquery to pure javascript
- Takes 1 year every single day.
- Understood control flow
- Build web application

[html, css, javascript] generate student ID Card from series called "The Underclass"(TH),

- 40 players on twitter
- Series director retweet
- Takes 1 week to do
- Self learning concept shortest path algorithm
  - Takes 3 months to understand
- Pratice coding algorithm calculate matrix like NumPy
   [python]
  - Takes 2 months to do

## SOFTWARE SKILLS

Expert





- · Corporate identity
- Retouching
- Various offline media
- Drafting



Portfolio graphic design https://prapask.wordpress.com/